Guide to the Frick Fine Arts Library Artist Files, 1892-1990 FFAL.002
ULS Frick Fine Arts Library
- Multiple Artist Files, I.; 259 folders
  - Pm-Por (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 183)
    Podwal, Mark H., 1945-; Polasek, Albin, 1879-1965; Polesello, Rogelio, 1939-; Pollack, Reginald; Poleskie, Steve, 1938-; Pollet, Joseph C., 1897-1979; Pointon, Robert; Poliakoff, Serge, 1900-1969; Pomeroy, Jim, 1945-1992; Pomodoro, Giò, 1930-2002; Pond, Clayton; Ponti, Gio, 1891-1979; Porter, Fairfield; Poons, Larry; Poor, Anne, 1918-; Poor, Henry Varnum, 1887-1970; Popov, Nikolai, 1938-; Porter, Eliot, 1901-1990; Porter, Katherine; Portocarrero, René, 1912-1985; Porcella, Yvonne; Portinari, Cândido, 1903-1962
  - Pos-Poz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 184)
    Potthast, Edward, 1857-1927; Potts, Don; Pousette-Dart, Nathaniel, 1886-1965; Poussin, Nicolas, 1594?-1665; Poveda, Carlos, 1940-; Powell, Edward; Powers, Hiram, 1805-1873; Pozzatti, Rudy, 1925-
  - Pp-Pre (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 185)
    Prado, Antonio; Prado, Gina; Prat, Juan; Pratt, Christopher; Pratt, Vernon, 1940-2000; Prendergast, Maurice, 1858-1924; Presas, Leopoldo, 1915-2009; Presno, Lincoln, 1917-1991; Presser, Josef, 1906-1967; Preston, James M.; Preston, James M., 1873-1962; Previtali, Andrea, approximately 1470-1528; Prezzi, Wilma M., 1915-
  - Prf-Prz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 186)
    Price, Alan; Price, Kenneth, 1935-2012; Price, Lucien, 1883-1964; Princeteau, René, 1843-1914; Prins, Pierre, 1838-1913; Priore, Luella; Priou, Louis; Prip, John; Proctor, Earl L.; Proetz, Victor, 1897-1966; Proffitt, Stacy; Prokop, Cliff; Prosperi, Warren; Provisor, Janis, 1946-
  - Ps-Pz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 187)
    Pucciarelli, Mario, 1928-; Puccinelli, Raimondo, 1904-1986; Putnam, Brenda, 1890-1975; Putterman, Florence, 1927-; Puvis de Chavannes, Pierre, 1824-1898
  - Q (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 188)
    Qassar, Abdulla; Qatami, Bader; Qattan, Khalifa, 1934-; Qualters, Robert; Quastler, Gertrude, 1909-1963; Quence, Raymond; Quinio, Lou; Quinn, Norman "Butch"; Quirk, Thomas
  - Raa-Ras (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 189)
    Rabinovitz, Marvin; Radosevich, Roseann; Radulovic, Savo; Raffaele, Joe; Ragouzeos, Leonard; Raid, Tiit; Ramos, Mel, 1935-; Ramírez Villamizar, Eduardo, 1923-2004; Rankine, V. V., 1920-2004; Raschen, Carl; Rasmussen, Peter; Rasmusson, Daniel
  - Rat-Raz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 190)
    Rattner, Abraham; Rauschenberg, Robert, 1925-2008; Ravizza, Ugo; Raymond, Richard C.; Rayo, Omar, 1928-2010
  - Rb-Reic (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 191)
    Reason, Cyril; Rebay, Hilla, 1890-1967; Rebaza, Gilberto; Rederer, Franz, 1899-1965; Redouté, Pierre Joseph, 1759-1840; Regney, John T.; Reiback, Earl M., 1931-2006; Reichek, Elaine; Reichek, Jesse, 1916-; Reichert, Donald, 1912-1982; Reichlich, Marx
  - Reid-Rend (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 192)
    Reifel, Noel; Reindorf, Samuel, 1914-1988; Reinhardt, Siegfried, 1925-1984; Reisman, Phillip; Reiss, Winold, 1886-1953; Rembrandt Harmenszoon van Rijn, 1606-1669; Remington, Deborah; Remington, Frederic, 1861-1909; Rendleman, Mark; Rendón Seminario, Manuel, 1894-1980
  - Rene-Richa (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 193)
    Includes Auguste Renoir exhibition catalogs: "Renoir Exhibition" Dalzell Hatfield Galleries, Los Angeles, 1943 and "Renoir, Degas Sculptures and Drawings" Charles E. Slatkin Galleries Galleries, New York, undated.
    Renninger, Katharine Steele, 1925-; Renoir, Auguste, 1841-1919; Renouf, Emile; Renteria, Philip; Resch, Fran; Ret, Etienne; Reyneau, Betsy Graves; Rezvani, Shahrokh, 1943-; Rheade, Frederick Hurten; Rhodes. Daniel; Rich, Garry; Richardson, Constance, 1905-; Richardson, Sam, 1934-
  - Richb-Rick (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 194)
    Richenburg, Robert; Richet, Leon; Richier, Germaine, 1902-1959; Richter, Edouard Frederic Wilhelm; Richter, Klaus, 1887-1948; Rickey, George
  - Rico-Riz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 195)
    Rico di Candia, Andrea; Rico, Martín, 1833-1908; Rifka, Judy, 1945-; Rigaud, Jean Claude; Rij-Rousseu, Jeanne; Ringgold, Faith; Ripper, Rudolph Charles von; Ripps, Rodney, 1950-; Rismiller, Jerry; Ritchie, Charles, 1954-; Rittenberg, Lawrence; Rivers, Larry, 1925-2002; Riverón, Enrique; Rix, Julian; Rizo-Patron, Beth Potter
  - Rj-Rock (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 196)
    Robbins, Gary; Roberts, Priscilla, 1916-; Roberts, Velma E.; Robertson, Don; Robie, Jean Baptiste; Robinson, Alexander, 1867-1952; Robinson, Boardman, 1876-1952; Robinson, David; Robinson, Nevin; Robinson, Theodore, 1852-1896; Robus, Hugo, 1885-1964; Roca Rey, Joaquin; Rocco, Michael P., 1926-; Rochegrosse, Georges, 1859-1938; Rockburne, Dorothea; Rockefeller, Mimi Sammis; Rockwell, Peter
  - Rocl-Rom (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 197)
    Roda, Juan Antonio; Rodchenko, Aleksandr Mikhaĭlovich, 1891-1956; Rodde, Michel, 1913-; Rodia, Simon, 1879-1965; Rodin, Auguste, 1840-1917; Rodríguez, Hugo, 1929-; Rodums, Oliver; Roerich, Nicholas, 1874-1947; Roesch, Kurt, 1905-1984; Roessler, Herman; Rogers, Gertrude; Rogers, John, 1829-1904; Rogers, Mondel, 1946-; Rogers, Roy David; Rohner, Georges, 1913-2000; Rolando, Maruja; Rollins, Carl Purington, 1880-1960; Romberg, Osvaldo, 1938-; Rombola, John; Romero, Alejandro; Romulo, Teodulo; Román, Nelson
  - Ron-Rosenberg (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 198)
    Rood, John, 1902-1974; Roqueplan, Camille, 1803-1855; De Rosa, Maurizio, 1971-; Rosado del Valle, Julio, 1922-; Rosano, Aureleo, 1939-; Rosas, Mel; Rose, Herman; Rose, Peter; Rosen, Charles, 1878-1950; Rosen, Joseph; Rosenberg, Samuel, 1896-1972
  - Rosenblum-Roso (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 199)
    Rosenblum, Jay; Rosenblum, Richard, 1940-2000; Rosenquist, James, 1933-; Rosenthal, Doris Patty, 1889-1971; Rosenthal, Tony, 1914-2009; Roslin, Alexander, 1718-1793; Rosofsky, Seymour, 1924-1981
  - Rosp-Rot (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 200)
    Includes Mark Rothko exhibition catalog: "Mark Rothko: Works on Pape,r" National Gallery of Art, May 6-August 5, 1984.
    Romano, Emanuel, 1897?-1984; Ross, Charlotte; Ross, Denman Waldo, 1853-1935; Ross, John, 1921-; Rosset-Granger, Paul Edouard; Rossi, Aldo, 1931-1997; Rostek, Phil; Rote, Dorothy; Roters, Carl, 1898-1989; Rothe, G. H. (Gatja Helgart), 1935-; Rothko, Mark, 1903-1970; Rothwell, Elizabeth
  - Rou-Roz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 201)
    Rouse, Jeffrey P.; Rousse, Georges, 1947-; Rousseau, Henri, 1844-1910; Rousseau, Théodore, 1812-1867; Roux, Pierre; Rowe, Guy, 1894-1969; Rowlands, Tom; Rowlandson, Thomas, 1756-1827; Rowley, Catherine; Roy, John, 1930-2001; Roy, Pierre, 1880-1950
  - Rp-Rz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 202)
    Includes Peter Paul Rubens exhibition catalog: "Peter Paul Rubens: Loan Exhibition for the benefit of the United Hospital Fund of New York" Schaeffer & Brandt, Inc., New York, November 23-December 19, 1942.
    Ruane, Patrick M.; Rubalcava, Cristina, 1943-; Rubens, Peter Paul, 1577-1640; Rubenstein, Lewis W. (Lewis William), 1908-; Ruckle, Ernest; Ruda, Edwin; Ruddy, Tom; Ruellan, Andrée, 1905-2006; Ruscha, Edward; Russell, Alfred, 1920-2007; Russell, Charles M. (Charles Marion), 1864-1926; Russell, Joan; Russell, Penny; Ruthenbeck, Reiner, 1937-; Ryan, Anne, 1889-1954; Ryder, Mahler; Ryerson, Margery
  - Saa-Sal (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 203)
    Saarinen, Lilian Swann, 1912-; Sabean, Samuel; Sabin, Hilbert; Sachs, Bernard; Safer, John; Safran, Bernard, 1924-; Sage, Kay; Saint-Phalle, Niki de, 1930-2002; Salancon, Eugenie; Salazar, Toño, 1897-1986; Salemme, Attilio, 1911-1955; Salemme, Lucy; Salerno, Charles; Salmon, Robert, 1775- approximately 1848; Saltzman, William, 1916-; Saluja, Harish; Salveson, Douglas
  - Sam-Sar (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 4, Folder 204)
    Samant, Mohan, 1926-2004; Samaras, Lucas, 1936-; Samsonian, Simon; Samstag, Gordon; Samuels, Diane; Sánchez, Humberto Jaimes, 1930-2003; Sandecki, Albert; Sander, Ludwig, 1906-; Sanders, Marianne; Sandino, Pedro; Sanfilippo, Antonio, 1923-1980; Sanford, Edward Field, Junior, 1886-1951; Sanguino, Luis Antonio; Sansó, Juvenal, 1929-; Sargent, John Singer, 1856-1925; Sarka, Charles N. (Charles Nicholas), 1879-1960
  - Sas-Schap (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 205)
    Saslow, Herbert; Sassone, Marco; Satterwhite, Richard T.; Sauer, Emil A.; Sava, Virgil; Savage, Naomi, 1927-; Savelli, Angelo, 1911-1995; Savinar, Tad; Saxe, Adrian Anthony, 1943-; Scarff, Tom; Scarvaglione, Concetta; Schabacker, Betty; Schanker, Louis, 1903-1981; Schantz, Frances Kratz; Schapiro, Miriam, 1923-2015
  - Schaq-Schi (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 206)
    Scharf, William, 1927-; Scharl, Josef, 1896-1954; Schary, Saul, 1904-1978; Scheibler, Frederick Gustavus, 1872-1958; Schell, Susan Gertrude; Scheuch, Harry; Schiele, Egon, 1890-1918; Schille, Alice, 1869-1955; Schippers, Wim T.; Schiwetz, Berthold Tex, 1909-1971
  - Schj-Schoe (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 207)
    Schlemmer, Oskar, 1888-1943; Schmeidler, Blanche; Schnakenberg, H. E. (Henry Ernest), 1892-1970; Schneebaum, Tobias; Schnier, Jacques, 1898-1988; Schnitzler, Max; Schock, Maya; Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951; Schoener, Jason; Schoettle, Marc
  - Schof-Schr (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 208)
    Schöffer, Nicolas, 1912-1992; Scholder, Fritz, 1937-2005; Schonbauer, Henry; Schonzeit, Ben, 1942-; Schor, Ilya; Schrag, Karl; Schrayer, Grover J.; Schreiber, Georges, 1904-1977; Schreuder, Jan, 1904-1964; Schreyer, Adolf, 1828-1899; Schreyvogel, Charles, 1861-1912; Schroeder, Sara A.; Schryver, Louis de
  - Schs-Scz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 209)
    Schueler, Jon, 1916-1992; Schuffenecker, Claude Emile, 1851-1934; Schugar, Leonard; Schülein, Julius W. (Julius Wolfgang), 1881-1970; Schultz, Bernard, 1948-; Schur, Esti; Schurr, Claude; Schwalb, Harry; Schwartz, Aubrey; Schwartz, Barbara, 1948-2006; Schwartz, Buky, 1932-2009; Schwarz, Reiner, 1940-; Schwarzburg, Peter, 1933-; Schwedler, William, 1942-; Schweitzer, Gertrude, 1909-; Schwitters, Kurt, 1887-1948; Sciavarrello, Nunzio; Scofield, Karen; Scott, Bill; Scurlock, Mary
  - Sd-Seli (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 210)
    Seago, Edward, 1910-1974; Seamon, D. Omer, 1911-1997; Searle, Ronald, 1920-2011; Seawell, Thomas; Sebire, Gaston; Seckar, Alvena, 1916-; Seeley, George H., 1880-1955; Segal, George, 1924-2000; Segui, Antonio, 1934-; Segy, Ladislas; Seidelhuber, Heidi; Seitz, Gustav; Seitz, John; Seley, Jason, 1919-1983; Seliger, Charles, 1926-2009; Seligmann, Kurt, 1900-1962
  - Selj-Sez (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 211)
    Includes Georges Seurat exhibition catalog: "Seurat: Paintings and Drawings," Knoedler Galleries, New York, April 19-May 7, 1949.
    Sellstedt, Lars Gustaf, 1819-1911; Selwitz, Ruth; Semeghini, Pio, 1878-1964; Sempé, 1932-; Senovich, Gloria Soderhiem; Sepeshy, Zoltan, 1898-1974; Serisawa, Sueo; Sermas, Gus; Serpa, Ivan, 1923-1973; Serra, Richard, 1939-; Serrier, Jean-Pierre, 1934-; Seurat, Georges, 1859-1891
  - Sf-Shee (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 212)
    Shahn, Jonathan; Shalom, of Safed, 1887-1980; Shapiro, David, 1916-2005; Shapiro, Dee; Shapiro, Joel; Shapiro, Sadie P.; Shapiro, Shmuel; Sharits, Paul; Sharman, John; Shaw, Charles Green, 1892-1974; Shaw, Karen, 1941-; Shea, Judith, 1948-; Sheeler, Charles, 1883-1965; Sheets, Millard, 1907-1989
  - Shef-Shz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 213)
    Sheeran, Sandra; Shepler, Joseph; Shepler, Martha Fairchild; Sheppard, Joseph, 1930-; Sherr, Ronald; Shields, Alan, 1944-2005; Shih, Phoebe; Shinn, Everett, 1876-1953; Shirk, Jeannette C.; Shoemaker, Brad, 1953-; Shonnard, Eugenie Frederica, 1886-1978; Shore, Stephen, 1947-; Shorr, Harriet, 1939-; Shwachman, Irene
  - Sia-Sil (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 214)
    Sibley, Charles; Sicard, Pierre, 1900-1981; Siegel, Irene; Siegel, Isabelle; Siegl, Helen; Sikora, Zdzislaw; Silberstein-Storfer, Muriel, 1923-; Silva, Guillermo, 1921-; Silvera, Eudoro, 1916-; Silverberg, David; Silverman, Burt, 1928-; Silvette, David
  - Sim-Siz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 215)
    Simboli, Ray; Simkin, Phillips, 1944-; Simmons, Laurie; Simonds, Charles, 1945-; Simpson, David; Sinclair, Alfredo, 1915-; Sinclair, Robert, 1939-; Singer, Arthur; Singer, Clyde, 1908-1999; Siporin, Mitchell, 1910-1976; Siskind, Aaron; Sivard, Robert
  - Sj-Slz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 216)
    Slaney, Elizabeth; Slavick, Susanne; Slenker, Bob; Slenker, Jean; Slepak, Paul; Śliwiński, Leon; Sloan, David; Sloan, John, 1871-1951; Slobodkina, Esphyr, 1908-2002; Sloman, Steven
  - Sma-Smith, G (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 217)
    Smith, Carol Cook; Smith, Frank; Smith, Gordon A., 1919-; Smith, Gregory H., 1941-; Smith, Hassel, 1915-2007; Smith, W. Eugene, 1918-1978
  - Smith, H-Smith, R (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 218)
    Includes 1970 letter from Dwan Gallery regarding Robert Smithson's "Spiral Jetty" and the availability of the corresponding film for purchase, along with a print of one of Gianfranco Gorgoni's photographs of "Spiral Jetty."
    Smith, Susan; Smith, Tony, 1912-1980; Smith, Vincent; Smithson, Robert; Smyth, David, 1943-; Smyth, Ned, 1948-
  - Smith, S-Smz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 219)
    Snelson, Kenneth, 1927-; Snethen, Merrill; Snyder, Bill; Sobek, Richard; Sobel, Jehudith; Sokolowski, Linda (Linda Robinson), 1943-; Solari, Luis Alberto, 1918-; Solbert, Ronni; Soler, Urbici, 1890-1953; Soleri, Paolo, 1919-2013; Solotaire, Robert; Sommer, William, 1867-1949; Sommers, John; Sommese, Lanny, 1943-; Sonfist, Alan; Sonneman, Eve; Sonnenberg, Joan; Sorce, Anthony John; Soriano, Juan, 1920-2006; Sorman, Steven; Sotirakis, Lemonia; Sotomayor, Jaime
  - Sn-Sot (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 220)
  - Sou-Soz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 221)
    Souchi; Soulages, Pierre, 1919-; Soutine, Chaim, 1893-1943; Souto, Arturo, 1902-1964; Soutter, Louis, 1871-1942; Sovák, Pravoslav; Sowers, Robert; Soyer, Raphael, 1899-1987
  - Spa-Spz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 222)
    Spacal, Jože, 1939-; Spandorfer, Merle, 1934-; Spangler, Kitty; Sparks, Arthur Watson, 1871?-1919; Spear, Chip; Spelce, Fannie Lou; Spencer, Niles, 1893-1952; Spero, Nancy, 1926-2009; Speyer, Nora; Spicer, Clayton; Spinnenweber, Rosemarie; Spitzer, Neal; Spofforth, John; Sprague, Lorraine; Sprinchorn, Carl, 1887-1971; Springer, Cornelius, 1790-1875; Spruance, Benton, 1904-1967; Spruce, Everett, 1908-; Sprung, Sharon
  - Sq-Stan (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 223)
    Sramek, Donna; Stachura, Jozef; Stack, Gael, 1941-; Stallknecht, Alice, 1880-1973; Stalnaker, Budd; Stamos, Theodoros, 1922-1997; Stamsta, Jean; Stanczak, Julian, 1928-; Stangl, Heinz; Stanick, Peter, 1953-; Stankiewicz, Richard, 1922-1983
  - Stao-Ster (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 224)
    Stark, Jim; Stark, Larry, 1940-; Stark, Margaret; Stark, Richard Boies, 1915-; Stark, Ron; Stayton, Janet; Steele, Gordon J.; Steichen, Edward, 1879-1973; Stein, Harvey, 1941-; Stein, James; Steinberg, Saul; Steiner, Ralph, 1899-1986; Steinhardt, Jacob, 1887-1968; Steir, Pat, 1940-; Stella, Frank; Stelling, Jos; Stephenson, Susanne, 1935-; Stern, Janine; Stern, Marina; Sternberg, Harry, 1904-2001; Sterne, Hedda, 1910-2011; Sterner, Albert, 1863-1946; Sterpini, Ugo, 1927-2000
  - Stes-Stri (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 225)
    Stettheimer, Florine, 1871-1944; Stettner, Louis, 1922-; Stevens, Edward J.; Stevens, May; Stevens, Nelson; Stevens, Will Henry, 1881-1949; Stewart, Norman; Stillman-Myers, Joyce; Stilson, William H.; Stimmer, Tobias, 1539-1584; Stirbu, Stefan, 1939-; Stobart, John, 1929-; Stokes, Frank Wilbert, 1858-1955; Stoller, Karen; Stoltz, David; Stone, Michelle; Stone, Silvia; Strasen, Barbara; Strater, Henry, 1896-1987; Stratton, Grace Hall; Strawinsky, Théodore, 1907-1989; Strick, Ruth Cochran
  - Stro-Suth (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 226)
    Strocen, Stefan; Stroh, Earl, 1924-; Strom, Karen; Strombotne, James; Stromeyer, David; Strosberg, Rachel; Strothman, Randy; Strueber, Michael M.; Stuart, Michelle, 1933-; Suba, Miklos, 1880-1944; Sugarman, George, 1912-1999; Sullivan, Billy, 1946-; Summers, Carol, 1925-; Summers, David; Summers, Deborah; Sundberg, Carl; Sundberg, Craig; Sundberg, Wilda; Sussman, Arthur, 1927-; Sutherland, Graham Vivian, 1903-1980
  - Sutt-Sz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 227)
    Suttman, Paul, 1933-1993; Suzuki, James; Suzuki, Takasi; Svet, Miriam; Syberg, Fritz, 1862-1939; Symczak, Mark; Szalay, Lajos, 1909-1995; Szobel, Geza; Szyk, Arthur, 1894-1951
  - Taa-Tal (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 228)
    Tábara, Enrique, 1930-; Tábora, Fernando; Tacha, Athena, 1936-; Tack, Augustus Vincent, 1870-1949; Tafur, Alicia B.; Tagle, Augusto, 1918-1974; Takal, Peter, 1905-1995; Takis, 1925-; Talibah Fennell, Michelle; Talleur, John, 1925-
  - Tam-Tar (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 229)
    Tam, Reuben; Tamayo, Rufino, 1899-1991; Tanksley, Ann; Tanning, Dorothea, 1910-2012; Taper, Geri; Tàpies, Antoni, 1923-2012; Tarantal, Stephen
  - Tas-Tha (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 230)
    Tausik, Joan; Taylor, Andrea; Taylor, Brett; Taylor, Robert S.; Tempel, Ernst Wilhelm Leberecht, 1821-1889; Tenace, Ron; Tennent, Madge; Teraoka, Masami, 1936-; Tereshko, Daniel W.; Terris, Albert; Teske, Edmund, 1911-1996; Tharsing, Robert, 1943-; Thaulow, Fritz, 1847-1906
  - Thb-Thom (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 231)
    Theobald, Renee; Thevenet, Jacques; Thiebaud, Wayne; Thom, Robert; Thomas, Howard, 1899-1971; Thomas, Robert C.; Thompson, Barbara S.; Thompson, Bob, 1937-1966; Thompson, Janet D.
  - Thon-Tob (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 232)
    Thon, William, 1906-2000; Thöny, Wilhelm, 1888-1949; Tice, George A.; Tillim, Sidney, 1925-2001; Tillyer, William; Timberlake, Bob; Ting, Walasse; Tinguely, Jean, 1925-1991; Tissot, James, 1836-1902; Tobey, Mark
  - Toc-Tor (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 233)
    Todd, Mike, 1935-; Toledo, Francisco, 1940-; Tolegian, Manuel J. (Manuel Jerair), 1911-1983; Tomchuk, M. (Marjorie), 1933-; Topor, Roland, 1938-1997; Toribio, Antonio; Torres-García, Joaquín, 1874-1949
  - Tos-Tri (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 234)
    Includes Toulouse-Lautrec exhibition catalog: "Paintings, Drawings, Prints and Posters by Henri de Toulouse-Lautrec," March 6-April 20, 1947, Carnegie Institute, Pittsburgh.
    Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri de, 1864-1901; Touster, Irwin, 1921-; Townley, Hugh; Tozer, David; Trager, Phil; Trier, Hann, 1915-1999; Trivigno, Pat, 1922-2013
  - Trj-Tsch (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 235)
    Tromka, Abram, 1896-1954; Troy, Jack, 1938-; Troyon, Constant, 1810-1865; Trujillo, Guillermo, 1927-; Trujillo, Sergio; Tryon, Dwight William, 1849-1925; Tsai, Wen-Ying, 1928-2013; Tschacbasov, Nahum, 1899-; Tschernjawski, Alex; Tschida, Fred; Tschumi, Otto, 1904-1985
  - Tsd-Tu (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 236)
    Tseng, Hsien-Chi; Tucker, Norval; Tullis, Garner H., 1939-; Tunnard, John, 1900-1971; Turano, Don; Turnbull, William, 1922-2012; Turner, Edward Llewellyn; Turner, J. M. W. (Joseph Mallord William), 1775-1851; Turnier, Luce
  - Tv-Tz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 237)
    Twiggs, Russell, 1898-1991; Tworkov, Jack; Tyler, Gillian; Tyler, Kenneth E.; Tyler, Valton, 1944-
  - Ua-Un (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 238)
    Ubertalli, Hector; Uelsmann, Jerry, 1934-; Uglow, Euan, 1932-2000; Uhlmann, Hans, 1900-1975; Umbricht, Honore Louis; Underwood, Julian; Underwood, Loring, -1930; Underwood, Wm. Lyman, -1929; Unger, Douglas
  - Uo-Uz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 239)
    Urban, Reva; Urbhan, Mychajlo; Urdang, Bertha; Urquhart, Tony; Urry, Steve; Urueta, Eduardo; Utenkov, Demian; Utrillo, Maurice, 1883-1955; Uzzle, Burk
  - Vaa-Vander (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 240)
    Vaccarino, Robin; Valdivieso, Raúl, 1931-1993; Valentin, de Boulogne, 1591-1632; Valentine, DeWain, 1936-; Vallotton, Félix, 1865-1925; Valmier, Georges, 1885-1937; Valtat, Marie-Lucie Nessi; Valverde, César; Van Alstine, John, 1952-; van Bergen, Thierry; van Campen, Tim; van der Zee, James, 1886-1983; Vandall, Richard; Vander Sluis, George, 1915-1984; Vanderlyn, John, 1775-1852
  - Vandes-Ved (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 241)
    Van Hoesen, Beth, 1926-2010; Van Leyden, Ernst, 1892-1969; van Sciver, Lloyd; van Sciver, Pearl Aiman; Varga, Margit, 1908-2005; Varmecky, John A.; Varner, Charles; Vasarely, Victor, 1906-1997; Vasca, Pintura; Vasulka, Steina, 1940-; Vaughn, Nick; Vedovelli, Antonio
  - Vee-Vez (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 242)
    Vega, Jorge de la, 1930-1971; Vegter, Joop; Velasquez, Juan Ramon; Velde, Bram van, 1895-1981; Vénard, Claude, 1913-1999; Venturelli, José, 1924-1988; Vereshchagin, Vasiliĭ Vasilʹevich, 1842-1904; Verkauf, Willy; Vernier, Emile; Vernon, Gayle; Verostko, Roman; Vertes, Marcel; Vespremi, Laslo; Vestier, Antoine, 1740-1824; Veyrassat, Jules Jacques, 1828-1893
  - Via-Vig (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 243)
    Vibert, J. G. (Jehan Georges), 1840-1902; Vicente, Esteban; Vidal, Miguel Angel; Vidal-Quadras, Aleix; Vieira da Silva, 1908-1992; Viera, Ricardo; Viesulas, Romas; Vignoles, André, 1920-; Vigée, Louis, 1727-1767
  - Vih-Viz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 244)
    Vilaro, Carlos Paez; Villa, Miguel; Villacis, Anibal; Villegas, Armando; Villon, Jacques, 1875-1963; Vincent, Tom; Vinci, Leo, 1931-; Vint, Mare, 1942-; Viola, Bill; Virduzzo, Antonino, 1926-; Viskupic, Gary; Viteri, Alicia; Vith, Edward R.; Vivian, Cassandra; Vivin, Louis, 1861-1936
  - Vj-Vz (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 245)
    Vlaminck, Maurice de, 1876-1958; Vogel, Peter, 1937-; Vogt, David; Vollet, Jean; Voltz, Friedrich, 1817-1886; von Moschzisker, Berthe; von Overveldt, Nancy; Von Wicht, John, 1888-1970; Vonnoh, Bessie Potter, 1872-1955; Vostell, Wolf, 1932-1998; Voulkos, Peter, 1924-2002; Vourvoulias, Joyce; Vradelis, Scott; Vuillard, Édouard, 1868-1940; Vuillefroy, Felix Dominique de; Vytlacil, Vaclav, 1892-1984
  - Waa-Ward (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 246)
    Wada, Warner; Wagemaker, Jaap, 1906-1972; Waitzkin, Stella; Waldberg, Patrick; Walker, William Aiken, 1839-1921; Walkowitz, Abraham, 1880-1965; Wallace, Jerome; Walmsley, William Aubrey, 1923-; Walpole, Frederick A., 1861-1904; Walsh, Mary Sue; Wangu, Madhu Bazaz; Ward, Lynd, 1905-1985; Ward, Marc; Ward, Virginia
  - Ware-Wat (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 247)
    Wargo, Peter Jeffrey; Waring, Leila; Warkov, Esther; Warren, Leonard Deakyne, 1906-1992; Warshaw, Howard; Wasey, Jane; Waterstreet, Ken; Watson, Ronald G., 1941-; Watts, George Frederick, 1817-1904
  - Wau-Wed (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 248)
    Waugh, Frederick Judd, 1861-1940; Wayne, June, 1918-2011; Weaver, Greg; Webb, Frank; Webb, Kenneth, 1927-; Weber, Hugo, 1918-1971; Webster, Herman A. (Herman Armour), 1878-1970; Wedgwood, Geoffrey Heath
  - Wee-Wel (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 249)
    Wegman, William; Weidenaar, Reynold H. (Reynold Henry), 1915-1985; Weidl, Seff, 1915-; Weidner, Mary; Weiner, Abe; Weiner, Lawrence, 1932-2009; Weinman, Adolph A. (Adolph Alexander), 1870-1952; Weiss, Edward; Weiss, Lee, 1928-; Weiss, Milton; Welch, Robin, 1936-; Welch, Roger; Welliver, Neil; Wells, Richard Gordon; Welsh, Louis
  - Wem-Wez (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 250)
    Wescott, William Carter; Wessner, Robyn; West, Troy; Westermann, H. C. (Horace Clifford), 1922-1981; Westlund, Harry; Weston, Brett; Weston, Edward, 1886-1958; Wexler, Alex
  - Wf-Wik (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 251)
    Wheat, John; White, Bruce; White, Charles, 1918-1979; White, Tom; Whitlatch, Don; Whittredge, Worthington, 1820-1910; Whyte, Raymond; Wiedemann, Guillermo, 1905-1969; Wiener, Grand Pa, 1886-1970; Wiesenfeld, Paul; Wiken, Dick
  - Wil-Wind (File-cabinet 3, Drawer 5, Folder 252)